よし　行動開始だね！ ああ！
And providing guidance. He's telling me how to become stronger.
これがハンター専用サイト？
Interest x And x Curse
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]　ハンターライセンスを差し込み ライセンスコードを入力してください。
As they prepare to challenge Knuckle and Shoot, Gon and Killua are deep in thought.
バーテンダーに カーソルを合わせてみな。 [ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ] どんな情報をお望みだ？
The loser...
うわっ！　すごい量！
Hands his token to the winner.
さすがにタダじゃ 教えてくれねえな。
Gon...
まっ　仕方ねえか。 ２０００万　振り込み…　と。
As promised, I'm coming at you
モニターからオーラが！
at full power!
どうやら　このサイト 念能力者しか入れないらしいな…。
I have to be ready to take the hit... And counterattack!
あ…。
Don't follow him by sight.
制作者は　どうやら複数らしいが 目的は不明だ。
Sense his motions...
そいつらは　１００本のソフト 全てに「念」を込めた。
Through my aura!
ゲーム機は　コンセントを抜いても 動き続ける。 死ねば止まる。
A little late, but I sensed his approach!
ある所有者が　プロを含む５０名の ハンターを雇い　挑戦したが
But what's going on?
セーブポイントさえ見つかれば 戻れるらしいがな。 本当かな？
I feel power rushing through my body...
現在７本の『グリードアイランド』が 競売申請登録されているもよう。
It's time. Adding interest.
最低落札価格は　８９億ジェニー。 ８９億!?
Wh-What is this thing?
やっぱ　上がってるよ！ 発売価格より３０億も！
I let you borrow some of my aura.
入手難易度はＧレベル。 えっ？ えっ？
You let me borrow your aura?
金額面さえクリアできれば 入手は比較的　易しい。
Ten percent every ten seconds!
ふん　Ｇレベルか… 案外　低いな。
If you don't repay the debt, you'll bust. It's time.
この程度の品を 入手できないようじゃ
Adding interest.
自分を捜せっこない ってことだよね…　ジン
I call this ability "Chapter 7 Bankruptcy."
けど　金の問題は大きいぜ。
That's the mascot, Amortizing Power Redirector.
ねぇ　オークションって 俺達も参加できるのかな？
Attacking APR is a waste of time...
８９億なんだぜ！ 俺らが入り込む余地ねえよ。
It'll just hang around you,
telling you when your interest goes up.
ううん　買うほうじゃなくて 売るほうで。
It's both harmless and invincible.
売るほう？　そうか！
Though it can be an eyesore...
俺達も　お宝を探して 競売に出すんだよ！
It's time. Adding interest.
まず　一般ネットの フリーマーケットと
Again. It doesn't hurt at all...
オークションサイトだ。 そこで　掘り出し物を見つけよう。
Instead, I feel another power rush.
金を増やして『グリードアイランド』 絶対　手に入れてやろうぜ！
It's time. Adding interest.
おう！
It suddenly almost doubled?!
イェイ！ うわっ！
It seems you have no clue what I'm talking about. "180 aura" is a numeric measure
of your spiritual power.
残り　いくら？
Aura accumulates in the body, and your Maximum aura Output Potential (MOP) varies according to your training.
２人合わせて １０８４万ジェニー…。 はぁ…。 はぁ…。 クッソ！　最初は　いい感じで 金が増えてたのにな。
Also, there is a limit on how much
aura you're able to release at once, which can be raised through training. In other words, your POP, the latent aura inside you, doesn't matter.
だから　信用できる公共サイトだけ 使おうって言ったのに。 しょうがないだろ！
If you haven't trained to increase your AOP, Present aura Output Potential [POP]
Actualized aura Output Potential [AOP]
ヤバい所じゃないと 儲けが少ないんだから！ はぁ…。 はぁ…。
the amount of aura you can actually release, you'll be at a huge disadvantage. Get it, fool?
うまく行かないなぁ。
When you use Ken, you can sustain
では　諸君の成果を 見せてもらおうか。
a maximum 1,800 aura around your body.
「名女優　セーラの毛髪 ＤＮＡ鑑定書付き」。 「エジープシャ石墓　埋葬品 ミイラの右腕」。
When preparing for battle, you usually expend 1 aura per second.
「龍皮病患者の皮膚」。 「一角族の頭蓋骨」。
However, once the fight begins, you begin to use advanced techniques such as Gyo, Ryu, and Ken, which require considerable Nen.
俺が護衛団リーダー ダルツォルネだ　よろしく。
The stronger your techniques,
the more aura you use up. Got that, fool?
諸君らには　早速 任務に就いてもらう。 任務は　ヨークシンの ホテルの部屋まで
Your control is still weak, so you're burning 10 aura every second.
ボスをガードし　無事に送ること。
That's 600 aura you expend per minute in battle.
ヨークシン郊外にある リンゴーン空港までは 専用飛行船で行く。
In yesterday's fight, you ran
out after twenty minutes...
空港からホテルまで約９０分 専用車を使う。
So, in a regular fight, you used up 12,000 aura.
諸君達４人は 護衛陣形の一番外を囲む。
Then add your four Jajankens!
何か質問は？
Your AOP is around 1,800 aura.
ボスを狙う人物の心当たりは？ 答える価値もない愚問だな。 どういう意味だ？
But at the moment you called out "Jan"
to activate Jajanken, the aura focused
ボスは黒社会の要人だ 恨んでる人間は売るほどいる。 分かっていないようなので 言い直そう。
in your fist was over 2,000. That's due to its long charge and your defensive
sacrifice, done to focus aura in your fist.
恨んでいようが　いまいが　要は 実際に行動を起こすかもしれない 人物の心当たりだ。
A special provision covers such risks
attributed to special attacks.
敵が絞れれば　動機　性格 環境が分かり　対策が立つ。
You expended around 5,500 aura
with the first three Jajanken shots!
それだけ護衛の安全度が増す。 クラピカとかいったか？
That puts your total consumed aura at 17,500.
分かってねえのは　てめぇだ。 俺達は　誰が　いつ　どこから ボスのネオン様だ。 俺達は　誰が　いつ　どこから
As for the fourth shot... Right before your do over hit, you ran out of energy.
あっ！ どんな方法で襲いかかって来ても ボスを守る。 ウフ！　よろしくね！ 新入りさん達！ どんな方法で襲いかかって来ても ボスを守る。 それだけ頭に 叩き込んでおけばいい！ ウフ！　よろしくね！ 新入りさん達！ 敵の姿を勝手に想像するな。 ウフ！　よろしくね！ 新入りさん達！ 敵の姿を勝手に想像するな。
Assuming that you needed twice the
usual aura amount to complete the attack, the fourth shot required 4,000 aura.
近づくもの全てが　敵だ！
The amount of aura used up is
the same for Rock and Paper.
ボスに紹介する　来な。
However, Paper falls within a different category, and you haven't practiced much, so you used up 4,000 aura on a weak attack.
ん？　ちょっと！　あれは？
is around 21,500 aura!
やけに生々しいな。 ああ　本物の人間だ。
I wasn't expecting this kind of attack...
かつての仕事仲間だがな。
Looks like you're not good at math.
俺の教えを守らず 敵の偽情報に踊らされ
But I'm just getting started! Listen up, fool!
結果　護衛団はおろか ボスを危険にさらした。 従って　処分した 諸君らは　彼の代わりだよ。 行くぞ。
When your borrowed aura, including interest, surpasses your current remaining POP, you'll bust.
ボス　新入りを連れて来ました。
If you keep spending, your balance decreases... But the interest keeps skyrocketing!
どうぞ。
It's been a few minutes since we started.
それにしても ボスに対面した時は驚いたな。
It's time.
ホント… 黒社会の要人だっていうから
Adding interest.
どれだけ凶悪な ご面相かと思いきや…
Even after adding in the
かわいいお嬢さんだこと。
390 aura I've lent you, you're under 20,000.
お久しぶり　シャルナーク フィンクスも。
Basically, unable to use any Nen. It's too late to regret fighting me now, fool!
集合時間１０分前が常識だろうが おめぇらもだよ。 ボノレノフ！　コルトピ！ お前達も　一緒だったのか。
That's why he didn't use this ability earlier. He held back for my sake...
よぉ！ 久しぶりじゃねえか　お前ら。
Knuckle!
着いたぜ　団長。
Thank you.
今度の獲物は何だ？ 早く命じてくれ！
Here I come!
フェイタン組が夜に到着する 全員　揃ってからだ。 相変わらず　せっかちね。
That punch just now was around 150...
クソっ　まだ半日もあるのかよ。 おっ！　シズクじゃねえか！
You returned 150 to me,
but I lent you another 180.
どうも。
The net impact is that your
loan increases by 30...
もう一人の新顔は　まだなの？
What will you do now?
さぁ？　マチにでも聞いてくれ。
Until your debt is repaid, I won't take damage from your attacks.
これが９月の分です。
You managed to land more hits.
あれ？　ちょっと多くない？ ええ。 ロットフェリ様とトリンク様も ぜひ占っていただきたいと。
But ultimately, you only returned about 100. It's time.
もう　ヤダよぉ。
Adding interest.
これ以上　増やしたら やめるって言ったでしょ。 申し訳ございません。
That's just a drop in the bucket.
どちらも父君と 懇意にされておられる方でして。
You repaid less than half your
last interest payment...
で　そのパパは　どうしたの？ どうしても外せない会議が ありまして。
I won't let you launch Jajanken again.
どうせ　ゴルフか ハンティングでしょ。
Once your debt passes 10,000,
my victory is assured.
[TEL]
It's time.
パパ？　ネオンだけど…。
Adding interest.
すご腕の占い師だとよ あの娘。
Can't let him intimidate me. Neither of us knows anything
about the other's abilities!
多数　顧客に抱えてるって話だぜ。
I don't like hurting other people.
いや　むしろ逆だろう。 逆？ 娘を利用して　父親が闇世界で のし上がった
That's why I chose a power that only activates
…と　とるほうが正しいだろう。
when I must hurt someone.
だから　父親は異常に恐れている。
To give myself a weapon that only works
娘を失うことと 自分が押しのけて来た連中の 妬みによる報復を…。
against those I have no qualms about hurting. However...
「旅団」が１３人全員 一堂に会するのって
How? They're floating?! What kind of power is this?
何年ぶりだっけか？　フェイタン。
Should I attack first?
３年２か月…　といっても あの時とは２人　メンツが違うね。
Stay calm... Observe the situation with Gyo!
マチ　４番は…
He's not using In.
ヒソカの野郎は 今日は　ちゃんと来るんだろうな？
There are three floating hands.
知らないね　私に聞くな。 お前の役目だろ？ 「来い」と伝えただけだ。
That means, most likely, he's a Manipulator. That cage is also a mystery.
私　ヒソカ　嫌いね。
He doesn't need it if he plans to use
なぜ団長は あいつの　わがまま　許すか？
those flying hands to attack.
腕が　いいからだろ。
In other words...
ありゃ　戦いづれぇぜ　実際。
Touching those hands is dangerous!
それが何か？　団長がヒソカのこと 怖がってるいうか？　許さないよ。
Yo-yos, huh?
そうじゃねえけどよ。
Let's see what you can do.
ノブナガ　てめぇ さっきから黙って聞いてりゃ。 ちっとも黙ってなかったじゃ ねえか　フランクリン！
He's amazingly adept...
ほっとくね 久しぶり　じゃれてるだけよ。
He's fast!
ところで団長 全員　集めて　何する気だろ。
Those hands were just a distraction?
そりゃ　私達　盗賊 物　盗むに決まってるね。
Jump back.
そりゃ　そうだけど…。 はい　ホテルには 無事　着きました。
When facing an enemy you
believe to be stronger, you fight on the premise of escaping.
ただ　お嬢様の占いに 気になることが…。 「何もかもが値上がりする地下室
No way... That's no different from what I've always done. Use electricity!
他人と数字を競ってもいけない」。
Couldn't get the attack off!
このくだりから始まる詩が 他に３編。
My body won't listen to me...
つまり　４人の顧客に 同じ占いの結果が出たんです。
This... is my curse.
その４人の共通点は 今年の地下競売に参加する予定が あるということです。
His reaction was slow. Is something wrong?
[TEL]　地下競売に出ると 命が危ない…　という占いか。
Stop... Don't think about it. It's my bad habit.
恐らく。
His circumstances don't matter.
眠ることに関する言葉は 病や死の暗示です。 [TEL] 分かった　占いの結果は
Do my best to defeat him. Otherwise, I'm only insulting him!
それと　もう一つ。
He's strong and fast.
お嬢様は　自分が占った内容を 知りませんし ご自身を占うこともできません。
He probably has me beat in every area...
このまま地下競売に参加させて よいものかと。
That's right, Killua...
[TEL]　ダメだ！ 今すぐにでも連れ戻せ。
That's the way. Don't fight an enemy you can't beat.
しかし　やめていただくにも 下手な説得は逆効果になります。
I have to stop thinking that way!
お嬢様が本気で怒ったら 我々では手に負えません。
Your weakness is that you're
too quick to give up.
競売は お前達だけで落札するんだ。 [TEL]　分かりました。
Even when facing enemies with equal strength, you worry about how strong they are,
or what they might do to you.
ふぅ…。
If we're talking about a stronger
enemy, there's no question...
ネオン…。
You don't bother to think of how you could win. Running is your only option.
That's how losers think.
チッ　はぁ…　来ねえな。 もうすぐ夜明けね。
I realize that this isn't your fault. It's the fault of whoever taught you to fight.
ヒソカの野郎 今度　会ったら 八つ裂きにしてやる。
Habits that are burned into your
body and soul aren't easy to break.
おやおや 物騒な話をしているねぇ。
Somewhere down the line,
you'll leave Gon behind to die.
怖い怖い。
Forget it.
ヒソカ！　てめぇ！ 遅かったじゃないか。
You can't win.
君に「来い」って 言われたからねぇ。
My left eye?
フン。 団長　揃ったよ。
The left side of my face
団長！　今回は何を盗むんだ！
Was what happened earlier a fluke?
アンダーグラウンドオークションの お宝を奪う。
If you take damage without knowing why, get as far from the enemy as you can.
何のお宝を？ 古文書とか　団長　本　好きだし。
My curse saved me.
違うね　きっとゲームね。
But that isn't good enough!
世界一高いゲームが 何本か売りに出されるよ。
Suppressing that bad habit and forcing yourself
とりあえず 金銀財宝が基本じゃねえか？
to face enemies stronger than
you will take determination.
全部だ　オークションのお宝 丸ごと　かっさらう。
I must fight to win!
手ぇ出したら 世の中の　その筋の者達 全部　敵に回すことになるんだぜ！
I'm blind on the left side...
嬉しいんだよ！ 嬉しくてたまんねえ！
There it was again. You reacted quickly.
さぁ！　命じてくれ　団長！ 今すぐ！
No! I'm just running away! I haven't been fighting at all...
俺が許す。 殺せ。 邪魔する奴は　一人残らずな。
If you can't defeat Shoot tomorrow, you must leave Gon's side!
地下競売で　次の３つの品物を 必ず競り落とす。 金に糸目は　つけない。
I'm done running away.
「俳優　ソン・リマーチ 使用済みティッシュ
Electricity?
ＤＮＡ鑑定書付き」。
Scary.
そして　「クルタ族の眼球」 通称　緋の目。
Doesn't matter... Follow him.
なお　何者かが　このオークションを 襲うという情報が入っている。
Never overpursue. Go after him!
来る　奴らが必ず来る！
...did you know? What am I asking that for?
殺戮の盗賊　「幻影旅団」 それぞれの運命が絡み合い オークション１日目の朝が やって来た
were fighting for the tokens...